hey everybody welcome to this A1 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as I speak before we
start remember to download the listening
Time Podcast and if you want my
specialized training to help you improve
your listening then become a member at
patreon.com listening time and if you
want my Advanced podcast episodes then
become a listening Time family member
okay today we're gonna talk about some
of my favorite things we all like
talking about things we like and I
wanted to make a video about some things
that I like so first I want to talk
about my favorite dessert this is a
really hard one for me to choose I love
a lot of desserts and so it's hard for
me to decide which one is my favorite
but I think that right now now my
favorite dessert is homemade chocolate
chip cookies notice that I said homemade
there's a big difference between
homemade cookies and cookies you buy
from the store in my opinion homemade
cookies are much much better than other
cookies and the perfect homemade cookie
is the chocolate chip cookie in the U.S
it's really common for families to make
this dessert together usually children
help their parents prepare and bake
these cookies it's a fun activity for
the family and the result is delicious
okay next let me tell you about my
favorite month of the year this is
another hard one but I think that my
favorite month is April the reason is
because I really like sunshine and long
day days in April Winter is finally over
the days get longer and the weather gets
warmer I don't have to worry about cold
weather or rain this is perfect for me
okay how about my favorite sport my
answer to this question has changed many
times in my life when I was a young kid
my favorite sport was basketball I was a
big fan of the Los Angeles Lakers and I
played basketball on many teams after
that my favorite sport was football and
I really liked the Seattle Seahawks for
many years then my favorite sport became
soccer and I started watching it a lot
but now I don't know if I have a
favorite sport I don't really watch
sports anymore so it's hard to say but I
wanna mention my favorite sport to play
I've played many sports in my life but
the funnest one for me is golf in my
opinion it's the most challenging sport
it's really hard but once you start to
get better it's really fun alright
lastly let me talk about my favorite
language that I've studied I like all
the languages that I've learned but the
funnest one for me to study is Greek the
main reason why is because Greek has a
different alphabet I love the challenge
of learning a completely new system it's
really cool to see Greek writing and be
able to read it and understand it I also
really like the sound of the language
it's a beautiful language and it feels
good to speak it currently I don't study
this language so I've forgotten almost
everything but I'll definitely start
learning it again in the future alright
I hope you enjoyed this video I also did
a podcast episode about this topic so
you can listen to that if you want to
hear more before you go remember to
download the listening Time Podcast and
become a member at patreon.com listening
time to receive my specialized training
to help you understand native speakers
and if you want to reach an advanced
level of listening then become a
listening Time family member to receive
my Advanced podcast episodes also
subscribe to the channel click on the
bell and follow us on Instagram I'll see
you next time